LUIS RUJANA

+1 785-547-8358 Imrujanass@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/ Imrujana

LinkedIn: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ luis-rujana-a410a4112/

11470 NW 82nd Terr Doral, Florida 33178

PROFILE

Chemical Engineer and Web Developer with their sights set on a full-time developer position. Experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap and Node. Strong mathematical and analytical skills, fluent in English and native Spanish speaker.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, GIT, GitHub, jQuery, APIs, Comand Line, Bootstrap, Bulma. Advance Microsoft Office.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

meApp

- Responsive app that uses different APIs to display forecast, motivational quotes, NYT articles and user-created notes.
- In charge of working with the quotes API, user notes and UI of the app.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bulma, APIs, Local Storage.
- Imrujana.github.io/meapp project/

Weather Dashboard

- Weather and forecast app that shows the current weather and forecast of a specified city.
- In charge of building the entire application.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, APIs, Local Storage.
- Imrujana.github.io/weather dashboard/

EXPERIENCE

Production Manager, DP FOOD DISTRIBUTORS; Miami, Florida — 2017 - Present

- Achieve customer satisfaction by ensuring the best quality of products and services. Recognized by manager for excellent customer service.
- Oversee a workforce of 10+ employees in the manufacturing of baked goods. Ensure all employees follow industry standards and food safety procedures by doing periodic trainings to the staff.

 Strive to reduce expenses and increase productivity, handling purchases and controlling food waste. In directed contact with vendors for a better communication between them and the company.

Submission Officer, VFS Global; Caracas, Venezuela — 2016 - 2017

- Directly in contact with visa applicants, handled their applications and sensitive documentation. Recognized by direct supervisor for excellent customer support and integrity.
- Implemented successfully the used of last generation scanners for the applicant's documents, resulting in the reduction of the waiting time for the approval decision; all while fallowing strict privacy and safety policies.

Field Engineer Trainee, Schlumberger; El Tigre, Venezuela — 2015-2016

- Successfully learned to formulate drilling fluids for different fluid conditions, using a variety of engineering concepts and techniques.
- Adapted to the rig field "lifestyle", working 12+ hours a day on a field camp, while delivering results following company standards. Reported activities to superior managers and client representatives on location.

EDUCATION

UM Coding Bootcamp, Miami, Florida — Certificate of completion , Present

- An intensive 24-week long program dedicated to designing and building web applications.
- Skills gained: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js, Git, Bootstrap.

Universidad Simon Bolivar, Caracas, Venezuela — Bachelor in Chemical Engineering, 2015

- Bachelors degree: Chemical Engineering GPA: 4.2/5
- Skills gained: Engineering concepts, strong mathematical base, problem solving techniques.

REFERENCES

- · Carolina Gorrin, DP FOOD DISTRIBUTORS.
 - Email: cgorrin@donpan.com
- Nicole Orozco, VFS GLOBAL.
 - LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/nicole-orozco-sampayo-52b1657b</u>